A Guide to the Arlington Coalition on Transportation (ACT) Records, 1958-2001
Arlington Public Library, Center for Local History
- Blueprints, Maps, and Documents
  - Mapped November 1970 - March 1971 (Box 16)
    - Summary of Comparison of Alternative Systems
    - District of Columbia Interstate System 1971
  - Design Hearing Information (Box 16)
  - Display Items (1)* (Box 16)
  - Display Items (2)* (Box 16)
  - Display Items (3) (Box 16)
  - Display Items (4)* (Box 16)
  - Photograph of Battleship Missouri (Box 16)
  - Sketches (Box 16)
- OVERSIZE BOX 1
  - I-66 Corridor Transportation Alternates Study Preliminary Engineering Report, November 1973
  - I-66 Corridor Transportation Alternates Study, Draft Environmental/Section 4(f) Statement
- OVERSIZE BOX 2
  - Proposed Four Lane Multi-Modal Concept Final Supplemental EIS, Section 4(f), December 1976 (two copies)